Guide to the Records of the Institute of African American Affairs RG.9.8
New York University Archives
- Series II. Association for Education in Journalism (AEJ), 1970-1993; 7 Linear Feet in 7 containers.
  - Interns: Gordon Balkcom, 1981; cuid16285 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Interns: Jones, Michael, 1981; cuid16286 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Interns: Martinez, Marcos, 1981; cuid16287 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Interns: Reeves, Crystal, 1981; cuid16288 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Interns: Roberts, Sandra, 1981; cuid16289 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Interns: Rogers, Danita, 1981; cuid16290 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Interns: Rodriguez, (Jaime) Javier, 1981; cuid16291 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Interns: Tracey, Aldina, 1981; cuid16292 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Interns: Trouth, Audrey, 1981; cuid16293 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Interns: Tuitt, Ronnie, 1982; cuid16294 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, 1982; cuid16295 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Finances, 1982; cuid16296 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Final Report, 1982; cuid16297 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Forms, 1982; cuid16298 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Program Operation, 1982; cuid16299 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Interns: Ashley, Berchelle D., 1982; cuid16300 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Interns: Berjano, Lily, 1982; cuid16301 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Interns: Bellamy, Lisa, 1982; cuid16302 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Interns: Godley, Lisa, 1982; cuid16303 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Interns: Jones, Carla, 1982; cuid16304 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Interns: Thomas, Larry, 1982; cuid16305 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Interns: Walker, Yvette, 1982; cuid16306 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Class Arrangements, 1983; cuid16307 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence, 1983; cuid16308 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Final Report, 1983; cuid16309 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Finances, 1983; cuid16310 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Receptions, 1983; cuid16311 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Interns: Adrine, E. Marie, 1983; cuid16312 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Interns: Collison, Michele, 1983; cuid16313 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Interns: Goeude, Nicholas, 1983; cuid16314 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Interns: Hom, Genevieve, 1983; cuid16315 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Interns: Miller, Deborah, 1983; cuid16316 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Interns: Seymore, Kelly, 1983; cuid16317 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Correspondence, 1984; cuid16318 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Forms, 1984; cuid16319 (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Interns: Carol Bash, 1984; cuid16320 (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Interns: Valerie Boyd, 1984; cuid16321 (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - Interns: Leslie Doi, 1984; cuid16322 (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - Interns: Farah Griffin, 1984; cuid16323 (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - Interns: Joye E. Mercer, 1984; cuid16324 (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - Interns: Winifred Yu, 1984; cuid16325 (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - Interns: Lisa V. Bond, 1984; cuid16326 (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - Interns: Adrienne Johnson, 1984; cuid16327 (Box 12, Folder 48)
  - Interns: Roberto Santiago, 1984; cuid16328 (Box 12, Folder 49)
  - Interns: Angela L. Slaughter, 1984; cuid16329 (Box 12, Folder 50)
  - Interns: Wanda Renea Taylor, 1984; cuid16330 (Box 12, Folder 51)
  - Interns: Vivian S. Toy, 1984; cuid16331 (Box 12, Folder 52)
  - Class Arrangements, 1985; cuid16332 (Box 12, Folder 53)
  - Correspondence, 1985; cuid16333 (Box 12, Folder 54-56)
  - Final Report, 1985; cuid16336 (Box 12, Folder 57)
  - Finances, 1985; cuid16337 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Program Operation, 1985; cuid16338 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Receptions, 1985; cuid16339 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Interns: Lisa Best, 1985; cuid16340 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Interns: Karen Brailsford, 1985; cuid16341 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Interns: Crystal Hayling, 1985; cuid16342 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Interns: John C. Hopkins, 1985; cuid16343 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Interns: Lisa Lewis, 1985; cuid16344 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Interns: Mai-Lan Pham, 1985; cuid16345 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Interns: Inez Pinto, 1985; cuid16346 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Interns: Constance White, 1985; cuid16347 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Interns: Fredricka Whitfield, 1985; cuid16348 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Interns: Loretta Williams, 1985; cuid16349 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Class Arrangements, 1986; cuid16350 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, 1986; cuid16351 (Box 13, Folder 15-16)
  - Final Report, 1986; cuid16353 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Program Operation, 1986; cuid16354 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Receptions, 1986; cuid16355 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Finalists and Interns: Borum, Jennifer, 1986; cuid16356 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Finalists and Interns: Esters, Stephanie, 1986; cuid16357 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Finalists and Interns: Freeman, Ernie, 1986; cuid16358 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Finalists and Interns: Goodwin, Jesse, 1986; cuid16359 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Finalists and Interns: Guiden, Tyrone, 1986; cuid16360 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Finalists and Interns: James, Alva Marie, 1986; cuid16361 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Finalists and Interns: Jeffries, Ira L., 1986; cuid16362 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Finalists and Interns: Poe, Juanita, 1986; cuid16363 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Finalists and Interns: Salter, Allanah, 1986; cuid16364 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Finalists and Interns: Tassey, Elaine F., 1986; cuid16365 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Finalists and Interns: Turner, Dawn, 1986; cuid16366 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence, 1987; cuid16367 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Finalists: Karen E. Delgado, 1987; cuid16368 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Finalists: Sheridan Honore, 1987; cuid16369 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Finalists: Pennie Lee, 1987; cuid16370 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Finalists: Allison Louis, 1987; cuid16371 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Finalists: Annette Shaw, 1987; cuid16372 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Finalists: Kimberleigh Smith, 1987; cuid16373 (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - Finalists: Ayesha Wilson, 1987; cuid16374 (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Finalists: Janet Jun-Lien Wong, 1987; cuid16375 (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - Program Operation, 1988; cuid16376 (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - Finalists: Charisse K. Lawrence, 1988; cuid16377 (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - Finalists: John Yeh -- AEJMC Applicant, 1988; cuid16378 (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - Class Arrangements, 1989; cuid16379 (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - Program Operation, 1989; cuid16380 (Box 13, Folder 44)
  - Receptions, 1989; cuid16381 (Box 13, Folder 45)
  - Finalists and Interns: Kalena Hammock, 1989; cuid16382 (Box 13, Folder 46)
  - Finalists and Interns: Natasha M. Labaze -- AEJMC Applicant, 1989; cuid16383 (Box 13, Folder 47)
  - Finalists and Interns: Michael Edwin Watson -- AEJMC Applicant, 1989; cuid16384 (Box 13, Folder 48)
  - Finalists and Interns: Towanda Underdue -- AEJMC Applicant, 1989; cuid16385 (Box 13, Folder 49)
  - Class Arrangements, 1990; cuid16386 (Box 13, Folder 50)
  - Correspondence, 1990; cuid16387 (Box 13, Folder 51)
  - Forms, 1990; cuid16388 (Box 13, Folder 52)
  - Program Operation, 1990; cuid16389 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - AEJMC Applicant: Kimetris Baltrip, 1990; cuid16390 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - AEJMC Applicant: Efrem Keir Graham, 1990; cuid16391 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - AEJMC Applicant: Tanya Haughton, 1990; cuid16392 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - AEJMC Applicant: Elizabeth R. Mesa, 1990; cuid16393 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - AEJMC Applicant: Tara Roberts, 1990; cuid16394 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - AEJMC Applicant: Andrea Wiggins, 1990; cuid16395 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - AEJMC Applicant: Lisa Chin, 1990; cuid16396 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - AEJMC Applicant: Cheryl Hendricks, 1990; cuid16397 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - AEJMC Applicant: Sirena Huang, 1990; cuid16398 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - AEJMC Applicant: Kimberly Maxwell, 1990; cuid16399 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - AEJMC Applicant: Raoul Mowatt, 1990; cuid16400 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - AEJMC Applicant: Teresa C. Puente, 1990; cuid16401 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - AEJMC Applicant: Dara N. Shariff, 1990; cuid16402 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - AEJMC Applicant: Towanda Underdue, 1990; cuid16403 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - AEJMC Applicant: Valentina Wilson, 1990; cuid16404 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Class Arrangements, 1991; cuid16405 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Forms, 1991; cuid16406 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Program Operation, 1991; cuid16407 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Geraldine Alumit, 1991; cuid16408 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Marisol Bello, 1991; cuid16409 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Melinda A. Bond, 1991; cuid16410 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Stacy Coates, 1991; cuid16411 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Alicia Coulote, 1991; cuid16412 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Cora Daniels, 1991; cuid16413 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Heidi W. Durrow, 1991; cuid16414 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Patricia Edwards, 1991; cuid16415 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Grace Kyungwon Hong, 1991; cuid16416 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Sophia V. McGregor, 1991; cuid16417 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Kimberly R. Riley, 1991; cuid16418 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Jennifer Rodriguez, 1991; cuid16419 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Summer Internship Informational Packet, 1993 (Box 67, Folder 9)
- Series III. Director Files, 1966-2006; 22 Linear Feet in 22 containers.; 579.30 Megabytes in 51 computer files.
  This series contains paper and computer files generated by past Institute of African American Affairs (IAAA) Directors including Founding Director Roscoe C. Brown Jr. (served from 1969 to 1977), Acting Director Edward M. Carroll (served from 1977 to 1979), Earl S. Davis (served 1979 to 1994) and Manthia Diawara (1992-2018). Files include advisory group minutes; IAAA Director and staff correspondence; conference packets and notes; IAAA histories and annual reports; Dr. Martin Luther King, Jr. Program material; and Black Scholars Lecture Series speaker information. Articles and scholarly journals found in files throughout this series that pre-date the IAAA were likely accumulated for subject or research files by the Directors.
  This series also contains project files from 1979 to 1987 related to multiple scholarly monographs published by IAAA. The original monograph was produced by a group of Black scholars to commemorate IAAA's 10th anniversary in 1979. After its successful release, additional monographs were published in later years.
  - ABFA, 1990; cuid16420 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - ABFA -- Confidential For Adm. Report, 1990; cuid16421 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Martin Luther King Jr., 1987-01-15; cuid16422 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - African Materials, 1990; cuid16423 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - African Global Heritage Association, 1990-12-17; cuid16424 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - AMC -- Colleagues Group, 1986-05-08; cuid16425 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Association of Black Women in Higher Education, circa 1985; cuid16426 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Black Alumni -- Call-In List, undated; cuid16427 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Black Creation, undated; cuid16428 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Black Student Center, undated; cuid16429 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Black Family Conference, undated; cuid16430 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - IAAA Personnel Information, Correspondence, Articles, Flyers, undated; cuid16431 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - African Panorama, Correspondence, Articles, undated; cuid16432 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Events, 1983; cuid16433 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Faculty Resource Network, 1991; cuid16434 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Dr. Elizabeth Henshaw, Visiting Professorship -- Exchange, 1985-12-03; cuid16435 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Dr. Elizabeth Henshaw -- Nigeria [EMPTY FILE], undated; cuid16436 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Franco, undated; cuid16437 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Hutchins, Annette, 1986-10-16; cuid16438 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - IAAA Advisory Minutes, undated; cuid16439 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - IAAA History, undated; cuid16440 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - IAAA Annual Reports, undated; cuid16441 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Orde Coombs Collection, undated; cuid16442 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Rod Rogers Dance Company, 1984-03-29; cuid16443 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Soul of Reason -- Interview Questions, 1978-1979; cuid16445 (Box 16, Folder 4-5)
  - "The Black Woman and the Bicentennial Conference" Packet, Notes, and Correspondence, 1976; cuid16446 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Non-NYU Publications, undated; cuid16447 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Sixth Annual Community Service Award and Tribute, 1991-06-21; cuid16448 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Faculty Resource Network's Day Tour of Harlem, 1991-06-22; cuid16449 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - "African History: An African Perspective" -- Dr. Albert Adu Boahem, 1991-10-09; cuid16450 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - "Strengthening the Bond Between People of African Heritage" Lecture and Reception, 1991-10-14; cuid16451 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - ABFAS Open House Reception, 1991-10-16; cuid16452 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - "Forging Connections: African American and African Caribbean", 1991-11-13; cuid16453 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - The NYC 1992 Media Conference: "Accessing the Media in NYC", 1992-02-05; cuid16454 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Tisch School of the Arts Black and Hispanic Film Festival, 1992-02-18-1992-02-25; cuid16455 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Annual Choral Celebration of Black History -- NYU All University Gospel Choir, 1992-02-20; cuid16456 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Black History Month Celebration at the Bedford Stuyvesant Community Mental Health Center, Inc -- Keynote Speaker: Earl S. Davis, 1992-02-25; cuid16457 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - "An Evening With The Elders" Lecture and Reception, 1992-02-27; cuid16458 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - "Women As a Catalyst For Social Change" Lecture -- Mrs. Coretta Scott King, 1992-03-09; cuid16459 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - NYU Black Lobby Day Trip to Albany, 1992-03-17; cuid16460 (Box 17, Folder 2-5)
  - The 54th Massachusetts Colored Infantry Lecture -- Jacqueline Shearer and Professor Thelma Foote, 1992-04-23; cuid16464 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Black and Latino Awards Ceremony, 1992-05-02; cuid16465 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Welcome Reception for Dr. Manthia Diawara, 1992-09-18; cuid16466 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - The Coalition for Columbus on Trial: "500 Years of Cultural Resistance," and a Prayer March to the Negro Burial Site, 1992-10-01; cuid16467 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - The 1992 Christopher Columbus Consortium, NY Presents COLVMBVS RECONCILIATION FORVM: "THE WELL BEING IN THE XXIrst CENTURY", 1992-10-09-1992-10-11; cuid16468 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Christopher Columbus Consortium: Dr. Sandra Dernini, 1992; cuid16469 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Black Theatre in America: "Renaissance Revival", 1992-10-23-1992-10-25; cuid16470 (Box 17, Folder 12-14)
  - Black Theatre in America: "Renaissance Revival", 1992-10-23-1992-10-25; cuid16473 (Box 18, Folder 1-5)
  - "The Herencia Latina" -- Concert at Loeb Center, Featuring Willie Colon and His Legal Alien Band, 1992-11-06; cuid16478 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - "Passin It on" -- A Documentary Film About Dhoruba Bin Wahad and the Black Panther Part, 1992-12-05; cuid16479 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - James Weldon Johnson, 1990-11-12; cuid16480 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Nigerian National Culture Group, 2006-07-08; cuid16481 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - National Conference of Artists, 1994-04-05-1994-04-11; cuid16482 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Black Theater in America, undated; cuid16483 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - New York Urban Coalition Educational Summit, 1993-12-12-1993-12-13; cuid16484 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Festac Reunion, 1993-04-11; cuid16485 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Black Articles, 1966; cuid16486 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Black Articles, 1969; cuid16487 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Black Literary, 1969; cuid16488 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Conference on African and African American Studies in Atlanta, GA, 1969; cuid16489 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence of Roscoe C. Brown, 1969; cuid16490 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - IAAA Alteration of Office, 1969; cuid16491 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - IAAA Background Information, 1969; cuid16492 (Box 19, Folder 4-7)
  - IAAA Fundraising, 1969; cuid16496 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - IAAA Lecture and Seminar -- Report and Evaluation, 1969; cuid16497 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - IAAA Organizational Proposal Correspondence, 1969; cuid16498 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - IAAA Organizational Proposal, 1969; cuid16499 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - IAAA Progress Report, 1969; cuid16500 (Box 19, Folder 12-13)
  - Dr. Martin Luther King Jr. Center -- Correspondence, 1969; cuid16502 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Organizational Proposal for an Afro-American Institute at NYU in Honor of Dr. Martin Luther King Jr., 1969; cuid16503 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Publications at NYU: The Black Student at NYU, 1969; cuid16504 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Malcolm X -- Research Tape Transcription, 1969; cuid16505 (Box 19, Folder 17-22)
  - Washington Square Journal, 1969; cuid16511 (Box 19, Folder 23-24)
  - Black Articles, 1969; cuid16513 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Black Creation Magazine, 1970; cuid16514 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Black History Book Project, 1970; cuid16515 (Box 19, Folder 27-28)
  - Black Studies Coordinating Council, 1970; cuid16517 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Black Studies Courses, 1970; cuid16518 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence of Roscoe C. Brown, 1970; cuid16519 (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Democratic Republic of the Congo, 1970; cuid16520 (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - IAAA Activities, 1970; cuid16521 (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - IAAA Advisory Board, 1970; cuid16522 (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - IAAA Annual Report, 1970; cuid16523 (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - IAAA Black Studies Instructors: Billings, Charles E., 1970; cuid16524 (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - IAAA Black Studies Instructors: Goines, Dr. Leonard, 1970; cuid16525 (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - IAAA Black Studies Instructors: Kan, Michael, 1970; cuid16526 (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - IAAA Black Studies Instructors: Mitchell, Loften, 1970; cuid16527 (Box 19, Folder 39)
  - IAAA Black Studies Instructors: Young, Joseph, 1970; cuid16528 (Box 19, Folder 40)
  - IAAA Black Studies Instructors: Young, Philip, 1970; cuid16529 (Box 19, Folder 41)
  - IAAA Book Fair, 1970; cuid16530 (Box 19, Folder 42)
  - IAAA Conference Reports, 1970; cuid16531 (Box 19, Folder 43)
  - IAAA Evaluations, 1970; cuid16532 (Box 19, Folder 44)
  - IAAA Fact Sheet, 1970; cuid16533 (Box 19, Folder 45)
  - IAAA Fundraising, 1970; cuid16534 (Box 19, Folder 46)
  - IAAA Fundraising Benefit Performance, First Anniversary -- Steve Depass, 1970; cuid16535 (Box 19, Folder 47-48)
  - IAAA Lecture: Alex Haley, 1970; cuid16537 (Box 19, Folder 49)
  - IAAA Progress Report, 1970; cuid16538 (Box 19, Folder 50-51)
  - IAAA Proposal for Research: IAAA Training Minority Group Research and Evaluation Specialists, 1970; cuid16540 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - IAAA Publicity, 1970; cuid16541 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - IAAA Report -- Fall Term, 1970; cuid16542 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - IAAA Staff Bulletin, 1970; cuid16543 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - IAAA Staff Report, 1970; cuid16544 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - IAAA Steering Committee, 1970; cuid16545 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Journal of Negro Education, 1970; cuid16546 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Dr. Martin Luther King Jr. Center -- Correspondence, 1970; cuid16547 (Box 20, Folder 8-9)
  - Dr. Martin Luther King Jr. Center -- Publications -- The Niggafied Press, Volumes 3-8, 1970; cuid16549 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - NYU Publication: Internal for Faculty and Administration, 1970; cuid16550 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - The New York Urban Coalition, 1970; cuid16551 (Box 20, Folder 12-13)
  - Proposal for Research, 1970; cuid16553 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Sojourner Newspaper -- IAAA Publication, 1970; cuid16554 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Still Here Magazine, 1970; cuid16555 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Washington Square Journal, 1970; cuid16556 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Black Articles, 1971; cuid16557 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Black Creation, 1971; cuid16558 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Black Literary, 1971; cuid16559 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Black Studies Courses, 1971; cuid16560 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Black Studies Course Listing, 1971; cuid16561 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Black Studies Programs in the United States, 1971; cuid16562 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Black Studies Speakers, 1971; cuid16563 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Chancellor's Report -- IAAA, 1971; cuid16564 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence of E. R. Braithwaite, 1971; cuid16565 (Box 20, Folder 26-27)
  - Correspondence of Roscoe C. Brown, 1971; cuid16567 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Directories -- Business, Educational Periodicals and Journals, 1971; cuid16568 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - IAAA Activities -- Program Planning, 1971; cuid16569 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - IAAA Advisory Committee: Correspondence, 1971; cuid16570 (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - IAAA Black Studies Instructors: Coombs, Orde, 1971; cuid16571 (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - IAAA Black Studies Instructors: Exum, William, 1971; cuid16572 (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - IAAA Black Studies Instructors: Floyd, Art, 1971; cuid16573 (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - IAAA Black Studies Instructors: Furman, Roger, 1971; cuid16574 (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - IAAA Black Studies Instructors: Garriga, Jose, 1971; cuid16575 (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - IAAA Black Studies Instructors: Grimes, Larry, 1971; cuid16576 (Box 20, Folder 37)
  - IAAA Black Studies Instructors: Hall, Fred, 1971; cuid16577 (Box 20, Folder 38)
  - IAAA Black Studies Instructors: Holmes, Robert, 1971; cuid16578 (Box 20, Folder 39)
  - IAAA Black Studies Instructors: Jenkins, Adelbert, 1971; cuid16579 (Box 20, Folder 40)
  - IAAA Black Studies Instructors: Jordan, John Samuel, 1971; cuid16580 (Box 20, Folder 41)
  - IAAA Black Studies Instructors: Mickens, Al, 1971; cuid16581 (Box 20, Folder 42)
  - IAAA Black Studies Instructors: Ofonogoro, Walter, 1971; cuid16582 (Box 20, Folder 43)
  - IAAA Black Studies Instructors: Thornton, Virginius, 1971; cuid16583 (Box 20, Folder 44)
  - IAAA Black Studies Instructors: Walker, Dr. Wyatt T., 1971; cuid16584 (Box 20, Folder 45)
  - IAAA Fundraising, 1971; cuid16585 (Box 20, Folder 46)
  - IAAA Informal Seminar Series, 1971; cuid16586 (Box 20, Folder 47)
  - IAAA Orientation, 1971; cuid16587 (Box 20, Folder 48-49)
  - IAAA Staff, 1971; cuid16589 (Box 20, Folder 50)
  - IMANI Magazine, 1972; cuid16590 (Box 20, Folder 51-52)
  - The Institute of the Black World: Monthly Report, 1971; cuid16592 (Box 20, Folder 53)
  - Dr. Martin Luther King Jr. Center, 1971; cuid16593 (Box 20, Folder 54)
  - Dr. Martin Luther King Jr. Center -- Scholarships, 1971; cuid16594 (Box 20, Folder 55)
  - M.A. Program in Black Studies, 1971; cuid16595 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Minority Student Recruitment, 1971; cuid16596 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - NYU Publication: Internal for Faculty and Administrators, 1971; cuid16597 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Report to Ford Foundation -- IAAA, 1971; cuid16598 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - United States Exchange Program, 1971; cuid16599 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Washington Square Journal, 1971; cuid16600 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Godwin Agbeli's African Dance Class, 1972; cuid16601 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Art Collection -- Grey Art Gallery, 1972; cuid16602 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Black Articles, 1972; cuid16603 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Black Creation, 1972; cuid16604 (Box 21, Folder 10-11)
  - Black Films, 1972; cuid16606 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Black Studies Courses, 1972; cuid16607 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Black Studies in Higher Education, 1971-1972; cuid16608 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence of Roscoe C. Brown, 1972; cuid16609 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Directory -- Black Urban Alliances, 1972; cuid16610 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Final Report to the Ford Foundation, 1972; cuid16611 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Nikki Giovanni Reception, 1972; cuid16612 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - IAAA Advisory Committee, 1972; cuid16613 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - IAAA Association for Education in Journalism Program, 1972; cuid16614 (Box 121, Folder 1)
  - IAAA History and Research, 1972; cuid16615 (Box 121, Folder 2-4)
  - IAAA Informal Seminar Series, 1972; cuid16618 (Box 121, Folder 5)
  - IAAA Staff, 1972; cuid16619 (Box 121, Folder 6)
  - IAAA Training Program -- Community College Black Studies Instructors, 1972; cuid16620 (Box 121, Folder 7-8)
  - The Institute of the Black World: Monthly Report, 1972; cuid16622 (Box 121, Folder 9)
  - Dr. Martin Luther King Jr. Center, 1972; cuid16623 (Box 121, Folder 10)